[Music]
Born Free. As free as the wind blows.
As free as the grass grows. Born Free to follow your heart. [Music]
Live free, and beauty surrounds you.
The world still astounds you
each time you look at a star.
Stay free, where no walls divide you. You're free as a roaring tide, so there's no need to hide.
Born Free and life is worth living. But only worth living 'cause you are born free,
born free, born free
[Applause]
Good to see you. Yeah, sit down.
Boy, any idea how many records Born Free sold? Couple of million. Couple of million.
That's notthe only one you did. Well, we were lucky thatyear because the picture won and of course,
Born Free was the Academy Award winner too. So, we had a big year. Yeah. Let's talk about some of Roger Williams'sother hits.
Hey, you had a big hit series thatyear. Well, it was Born Free obviously yeah,
that brought back some fond fond memories. What other Roger Williams tunes that uh were right up there.
Well, we started out with Autumn Leaves. That wasway back in 1955. Anybody alive that remembersthat? It goes back.
Yeah, yeah. You've got a new album.
Yes, I do, it's called, Today My Way, and in it, we do Stevie Wonder, we do Wham, we do TinaTurner, Lionel Richie. You just go down the line,
Yeah, great music to listen to. Well you know,Gary you have to stay up with the times, that's for sure.
Yeah. Or you get left behind. Yeah,you sure do. Thank you Roger for being a part of this segment, Roger Williams, Born Free.